There's simply no way to shield
against every weaponized agent.
Instead, I can make
super-immune systems
by strengthening
the human cellular response.
Banner, I know
where you're going.
But manipulating the immune
system is dangerous and stupid.
The President's science
advisors made it absolutely clear,
no human subjects.
David, I have wonderful news.
I'm gonna have a baby.
What's it gonna be?
Look at that, Bruce.
Want a dinosaur?
Let's have a little fight.
You don't scare me.
That's a delicious eyeball.
You're big and green
and scary. I'm gonna run away.
Really, speaking of Cheryl,
guess what...
Bruce, you're hurt!
Jack hit him with the stick,
but Bruce wouldn't hit him back.
He just stood there, shaking.
It's okay.
Yeah, strange
he didn't make a peep.
Any other kid would've
wailed his head off.
That's Bruce. He's like that.
He's just so bottled up.
The samples we found in your
lab, they were human blood.
You've ignored protocol.
You had no right
snooping around in my lab.
- That's my business.
- Wrong, Banner.
It's government business,
and you're off the project.
Attention, all personnel!
Fail-safe has been initiated.
Gamma decontamination
will occur in 30 minutes.
Evacuate immediately.
I repeat,
evacuate immediately!
- Edith?
- David, what's going on?
- I gotta talk to you, Edith.
- Bruce, stay here.
What are you doing?
I'm trying to tell you
what's gotta be done!
David, please stop it! No!
David, no!
- No!
- Yes!
David! No!
Bruce.
Bruce, wake up, Son.
Bruce. Bruce.
Another nightmare?
I don't know.
I don't remember.
Hi, Mom.
Already off to college.
- I'm gonna miss you terribly.
- I'll miss you, too.
Please, come here.
Look at you. Soon to be
a great scientist.
- I guess. I mean, who knows?
- I do.
There's something
inside you so special.
Some kind of greatness.
I'm sure someday you're gonna
share it with the whole world.
But as far as I'm concerned,
security ought to be...
- Good morning, Dr. Krenzler.
- Good morning.
Security ought to be
beefed up a lot more.
In a place like this
you can't be too careful.
Bruce! Big day. Did
you sleep? I didn't sleep.
- I slept okay. ls Betty here?
- She's around.
I really gotta say, seeing
you in that styling headwear...
You're implying something
about my helmet?
You look like a massive nerd,
even around other scientists.
Can I just ask?
Were you wearing the helmet
while she dumped you?
See, it protects my very
important brain, Harper.
Go prep the samples.
- Hey. I found you.
- Betty, hey.
- I hate them.
- Wait, I just got here. Who do we hate?
The review board. We have to
make a presentation on Tuesday.
And you're gonna
make it with me.
- You think I should?
- Yeah, you're great with that stuff.
You start talking about
microbes and nanomeds,
you sound almost passionate.
I'm sorry. That was rude.
Look, nobody expects
this to be easy,
us working together
after being so close.
We were close?
Look, if I could be more
whatever, you know.
I'm just...
Don't. It's not
your fault, really.
You're just a by-product
of my inexplicable obsession
with emotionally distant men.
I'll get over us.
Good for you.
Anyway, I'm just really
stressed about this review.
If we don't get
impressive results today,
we're gonna have a really
hard sell come Tuesday.
Well, then,
let's go be impressive.
Harper?
- Ready when you are.
- Let's hit it.
Are we passing inspection?
Safeties all going green.
Countdown's started.
Nanomeds released.
Four seconds.
Okay, nanomeds fully dispersed.
Okay, let's hit Freddie
with the gamma radiation.
Gamma exposure.
Nanomeds now active.
Nanomeds
replicating cells on border.
It's working.
Cell copy to disassemble
ratio holding within 1%.
Imbalanced nanomed activity.
You wanna go to
the review board on Monday
and tell them we've developed a
brand-new method for exploding frogs?
Yeah, I think maybe
there's a market for it.
I mean, what if
there's a plague?
What have you had, Betty,
like, one beer?
I'm just... I'm just saying, you
know, frogs start falling from the sky,
who do they come to?
- We'd be world-renowned.
- Make any parent proud.
I bet they would be.
They actually did want me
to be a scientist.
I mean, your birth parents.
Guess we'll never know.
I don't understand why you
don't want to find out about them.
They're dead. They died before
I could remember anything.
Why do you always
come back to this?
Don't know.
I guess I figure there's more
to you than you like to show.
I guess there
couldn't be any less.
Right. So now we come
full circle back to that.
Nice work, Betty.
Betty.
- Glenn.
- Hey.
- Hi.
What happened to your uniform?
Oh, I switched over.
I'm still working
with your father, but...
Well, you know, the
military's subcontracting out
all the most
interesting work, and...
Can't argue with the paycheck.
I basically run all the labs
on the base now.
Hey, you're...
You're looking good.
You're the genetics expert.
Ah, the good old college days.
So, how's business?
What do you want?
All right,
I'll cut to the chase.
I've been hearing interesting things
about what you guys are doing here.
Your little molecular machines
have some incredible implications.
How would you like
to come work for Atheon?
Get paid 10 times as much
as you earn now
and own a piece of the patents.
- You just have to say the word.
- Two words, the door.
- General?
- Come in.
Talbot wanted you
to see this, sir.
It's about a lab Atheon is targeting for
acquisition and removal to Desert Base.
Why isn't it going through NSC?
It concerns your daughter, sir.
Hi. Sorry.
Hey, what happened to Benny? Is
he not working the night shift anymore?
Benny's dead.
I'm the new guy.
Oh.
- Good to meet you.
- Same.
- Let's try another.
- No, stay here.
- I look tired anyway.
- Yeah, but you look great.
What's the matter?
It's these dreams, Doctor. I keep
having them and they're terrible.
Tell me about your dream.
Well, it starts...
It starts with a memory.
I think it's my first memory.
It's this image I have
from when I was maybe
two years old.
Do you think it's just a dream?
No, I think it's something
that happened
when I was living at a
desert base with my father.
Anyhow, the dream goes on
and suddenly I'm alone.
That's terrible.
You know I'd never hurt you.
Hey, there.
What's your name, darling?
What's your name?
Okay. It's okay.
- I gotta talk to you, Edith.
- Bruce, stay here.
C, T, G, A,
G.
Bruce.
My Bruce.
Morning. Glenn dropped by.
- What's he doing here?
- You know, Dr. Krenzler,
you and I have never had the chance
to get to know each other properly.
Well, that's because I don't want to
get to know you, properly or improperly.
So leave.
Hey, no worries.
Let me give you
a little heads up.
There is a hair's breadth between
friendly offer and hostile takeover.
I've done my homework. The
work you're doing here is dynamite.
Think, GIs embedded
with technology
that makes them instantly
repairable on the battlefield
in our sole possession.
- That's a hell of a business.
- Well, it's not what we're doing here.
We're doing the basic science
for everyone.
You know, someday I'm gonna
write a book and I'm gonna call it,
When Stupid Ideals Happen
to Smart Penniless Scientists.
In the meantime, Bruce,
you will be hearing from me.
- About Glenn, I...
- There's nothing to talk about.
Okay.
I just wanted to say,
don't worry about him.
I'll handle it.
How'?
I'm gonna call my father, ask
him to exert some pressure.
Last I heard, you and your
father weren't speaking.
Well,
I guess now I have something
to talk with him about.
I think this circuit's
kind of fried. I don't know.
Maybe you wanna
come take a look at it.
Okay, I'll be right there.
The gamma's too high!
Bruce, I can't stop it!
Harper, get out!
Get out!
- How's Harper?
- He's all right.
You saved him.
I don't think he's coming back
to the lab for a while, though.
I don't understand
how this is possible.
You should be dead.
They worked,
the nanomeds.
I mean, I feel great.
I feel like...
I don't know. They
must have, like, fixed me.
Bruce, they've killed everything else
that they've come into contact with.
Are you sure the doctor checked?
The doctor gave me
the full workup.
He wants to know where
he can get what I'm taking.
I'm 100%.
More.
- What do you mean?
- Remember my bad knee?
Well, now it's my good knee.
Bruce, this isn't funny.
I was watching you.
You were gonna die, and I
was gonna have to watch you die.
Betty, I'm sorry.
Really.
Hey, I'm not gonna explode.
Okay?
Yeah.
You should get some rest.
And I'm fine, really.
I've never felt better.
Your name is not Krenzler.
It's Banner.
- What?
- Your name, it's Banner.
Bruce Banner.
Bruce.
- How did you get in here?
- I work here now.
In the labs. The late shift.
It keeps me close to you.
You always work so late
yourself with your friend Miss Ross.
No, no. Please.
Please. Let me.
You're not well.
You've had a terrible accident.
You're wondering
why you're still alive.
You're thinking
there's something inside.
Something different,
inexplicable.
I can help you understand,
if you'll let me.
If you'll
forgive me.
Look, mister, I'm sure I have
nothing to forgive you for.
So perhaps you should
leave now. I'll be fine.
You must know.
You may not want to believe
it, but I can see it in your eyes.
So much like your mother's.
Of course,
you're my flesh and blood.
But then you're something
else, too, aren't you?
My physical son,
but the child of my mind, too.
No. You're lying.
My parents died
when I was a small boy.
No, no, that's not true. That's
what they wanted you to believe.
The experiments, the accident,
all top secret.
They put me away
for 30 years. Thirty years!
Away from you.
Away from our work.
But they couldn't
keep me forever.
After all, I'm sane.
They had to admit it.
You see,
everything
your extraordinary mind
has been seeking
all these years,
it's been inside you.
Now we will understand it.
We will harness it.
No, don't answer it.
It's Miss Ross again.
There's something you need
to know about her, Bruce.
Something troublesome.
Let me protect you from her.
No. Get out.
- Bruce...
- Get out!
Sit!
We're gonna have to watch
that temper of yours.
You sure you're okay?
Yeah,
just glad to be out of bed.
Got a message from my father.
He's coming to see me.
Your father?
- When?
- Lands in about an hour.
The funny thing is,
he called me.
- Hi, Dad.
- Hello, Betty.
- Here, ma'am.
- Thanks.
- You're welcome. Sir?
- Thank you.
You're welcome.
- Look, I'm gonna get right to it.
- It's about Glenn, isn't it?
He's been snooping
around my lab.
Glenn noticed some things,
asked me to make some inquiries.
Are you here to question me?
No.
We've turned up
some surprising things.
This Krenzler you work with,
you know who he really is?
How much do you actually
know about him?
I think the question is, what
is it that you know about him?
Well, right now,
I'm not at liberty...
Not at liberty to disclose
it to me. Right. Right.
You know, I think I was hoping
that maybe this time you just
honestly wanted to see me again.
- You've got this all wrong, Betty.
- Do I?
Yes. I do want to see you.
I really wish that
I could believe you.
Everything
your extraordinary mind
has been seeking
all these years,
it's been inside you.
Hi, you've called
Dr. Krenzler.
Please leave a message
and I'll call you right back.
Bruce, hey.
Are you there?
Look, I think I screwed up.
My father...
It's like he suspects you
of something. I don't know.
I was so impatient, like always.
I didn't hear him out.
I don't know, I...
I just think that they're
planning something with the lab.
So,
Call me. Okay? Bye.
Betty?
Dispatch! Dispatch!
We have a 415 at the lab!
Send the Berkeley P.D. now!
Send them now!
Watch out!
- Edith?
- David, what's going on?
- I gotta talk to you, Edith.
- Bruce, stay here.
My Bruce.
Bruce?
There was some
sort of explosion.
They wouldn't let us
into the building.
I was worried about you.
Well, I'm okay.
What happened to you last night?
I had the most vivid dream.
It was like being born.
Coming up for air. Light
hitting my face. Screaming.
My heartbeat,
it was like boom,
boom,
boom.
- Were you at the lab?
- No.
But something...
And there was that man,
the one with the dogs.
Who?
That new janitor.
He said he was my father.
I'll get it.
My father.
My, my.
So this is the young
Bruce Ban...
Krenzler.
I think you left something
in your lab last night.
Mitchell, escort my daughter
outside. I'll join her shortly.
- I'd rather stay here.
- Now, Betty.
It's okay. I'll be fine.
Keep him under observation.
I'll be back.
- What?
- Your friend in there,
there's a good chance he's caught
up in some very bad business,
unfinished business.
And I promise you, I'm
gonna get to the bottom of it.
You have my word
I'll make sure he's cared for.
But as of right now,
he is incommunicado.
And for the next
few days at least,
you're gonna stay away
from here.
For your own good.
Okay, and that's for the new
guy on the night shift, right?
Great. Thank you.
I appreciate it.
Dr. Ross.
How unexpected.
Please come in.
I'm sorry to just show up
at your house like this.
I came to ask you something
that I really have
no business asking.
He told you?
- He said you talked to him.
- Oh.
Please sit down.
Bruce was at the lab last night.
He said that
you were there, too.
But he can't remember
much about it.
I need to find out
what happened.
So, you want to know
what's wrong with him,
so you can fix him?
Cure him, change him.
My father's with the military.
He seems to think he's involved in
some kind of threat to national security.
Your father. Ross.
You brought your father
down upon his head?
How little you understand,
Miss Ross,
and how dangerous
your ignorance has become.
- I'm sorry.
- Don't be sorry.
My son is unique.
That's why you can't
relate to him.
And because he is unique, the
world will not tolerate his existence.
Will they?
But you,
you try, don't you?
Yes.
And a very beautiful
woman like you,
your attentions
can't be completely unwanted.
Can they?
No.
Not with eyes like yours,
watching expectantly, lovingly.
But I'm afraid we're both
too late to help him.
There's nothing I can do
for him or for you.
Besides,
he's made it clear he wants
nothing to do with me.
His choice.
Now if you'll excuse me, Miss
Ross, I got some work to do.
And don't worry about the dogs.
You'll be fine. Just don't
look them in the eyes.
Goodbye.
He gets released, and a
month later your lab is destroyed.
What a coincidence.
So you're just not gonna
tell me where he is, are you?
How many times
do I have to tell you?
I'd like to help you,
but I just don't know.
You know who I am.
Right, Banner?
You're Betty's father.
You're a high-ranking general.
Let's cut the crap.
I'm the guy who had
your father tossed away,
and a lot more like him,
and I'll do the same with you
if I feel so disposed.
You understand?
If you had him tossed away,
then why are you asking me?
I don't remember.
I was always told
my father was dead.
Don't play with me!
You were four years old
when you saw it.
When I saw what?
You were right there. How could
anyone forget a thing like that?
What?
Oh, some more
repressed memories.
Just tell me.
I'm sorry, son.
You're an even more screwed-up
mess than I thought you'd be.
Until we get to
the bottom of this,
your lab has been declared
a top-secret military site,
and you're not gonna get a
security clearance to get back into it
or any other lab that's doing
anything more interesting
than trying to figure out the
next generation of herbal hair gel.
One more thing.
If you ever come
within 1,000 yards
of my daughter again,
I'll put you away for
the rest of your natural life.
Dogs!
Go! Go get her!
And let nothing stand
in your way!
Go!
- Hello?
- Bruce?
So, they think they can just
throw you away as they did me.
What's wrong with me?
What did you do to me?
I got a visit today.
A very unwelcome visit.
I'm afraid my hand
is being forced.
What did you do to me?
You so much want to know,
don't you?
But I think no explanation
will serve you half as well
as the experience.
In any case, I still don't
quite understand it myself.
If they'd only let me
work in peace...
Of course, my betters
would have none of that.
So you experimented
on yourself, didn't you?
And passed on to me, what?
An alteration. Genetic.
A deformity. I guess
you could call it that.
But an amazing strength, too.
And now, finally unleashed,
I can harvest it.
No.
You'll do no such thing. I will
isolate it and treat it myself.
I'll remove it, and I'll kill it
before it does any real harm.
I'll bet you and your Betty
would love to destroy it.
But would you really destroy
part of yourself?
I don't think so.
And as for Betty,
I'm sending her a surprise visit
from some four-legged friends of mine.
You see, I've managed to culture
some of your very own DNA, Bruce,
and the results are tremendous.
They're unstable,
but very powerful.
What about my DNA?
Let's just wait and see what
Betty makes of the results, huh?
No. You're crazy.
I won't let you.
Get your hands off of me.
- Talbot, what's this...
- Inside, asshole. I wanna talk to you.
Listen to me, my father's
going after Betty...
What makes you think
you can go behind my back
and get Ross to cut me out, huh?
Listen to me!
Betty's in trouble!
You pathetic freak.
Betty's in danger. I swear
to you, she'll be killed.
I can state the obvious.
Something tells me you
aren't in much of a position
to be making
stupid threats to anyone.
- Talbot.
- Yeah?
You're making me angry.
Oh, am I?
My God, fire! Open fire!
Bruce?
He sent these dogs, didn't he?
But I killed them!
My God.
It must be the nanomeds.
It must be the gamma exposure.
But we've never seen
any effect like this before.
No. Deeper.
The gamma just unleashed
what was already there.
Unleashed what?
Me.
It.
It's okay.
What were those animals?
My father sent them.
He is my father.
He wanted me to change.
He wanted me to change
into that mindless hulk.
Why would he want that?
Can you remember anything?
Is there anything
from when you were changed?
It was like a dream.
About what?
Rage.
Power.
And freedom.
Hello? Sir.
- Hello.
- Dad?
Betty! Are you all right?
I'm scared.
I need your help.
Where are you?
How are you?
Okay, I guess.
I think that somehow
your anger is triggering
the nanomeds.
How could it? We designed them
to respond to physical damage.
Emotional damage
can manifest physically.
Like what?
Serious trauma.
Repressed memories.
Your father grilled me about something
that happened to me from early childhood
that I'm supposed to remember.
- He did?
- It sounded bad, but...
I honestly don't remember.
The thing that worries me
is
A physical wound is finite,
but with emotions,
what's to say it won't
just go on and on
and start a chain reaction?
You know
what scares me the most?
When it happens,
when it comes over me
and I totally lose control,
I like it.
It's okay. I got you.
I'm sorry.
You'll be okay.
It's just to make you sleep.
Target down. Target secure.
I'm going to take you
someplace safe.
Okay? Bruce?
Bruce?
Clear!
- Attention on deck.
- Carry on.
We're buried out here
in the middle of nowhere.
How long are you
gonna keep him sedated?
For the rest of his
natural life, if I have to.
- You said I could trust you.
- I'm your father.
You can trust me to do what I think
is right, not what you think you want.
- He is a human being.
- He is also something else.
Suppose he gets out, has
one of his little mood swings
in a populated area.
Yes, I'm aware of
the potential danger.
I'm also aware that
he saved my life.
Yeah, from a mutant
French poodle.
I'm indebted to him for that.
He also put three men in a
hospital, and Talbot's barely walking!
- What do you want me to do?
- I want you to help him!
Why is he such a threat to you?
Because I know
what he comes from.
He is his father's son,
every last molecule of him.
He says he doesn't
know his father,
but he's workin' in the same
exact goddamn field his father did.
So either he's lyin' or it's
somethin' worse, and he's...
What?
Predestined to follow
in his father's footsteps?
I was gonna say "damned."
Of course you were.
But I'm a scientist.
As a scientist, I believe we can
figure this out and he can be helped.
I know you do.
Whether you know or care,
I've got a lot of pride
in what you've done.
But this is too big for you.
Look, I know the government thinks
they have a weapon on their hands.
Otherwise, he'd be dead by now.
They can probe and prod
all they want,
and in the meanwhile,
just let me try to help him.
Nobody knows him
better than I do.
What did David Banner do to him?
- Cover left.
- Clear left.
Cover right!
What's happening here?
My hand.
You see, the strength
of my son's DNA
combined with nanomed
reconstruction...
You see, I can partake with
the essences of all things.
Gonna have to ask you to
put your hands up, pal, okay?
Nice and easy.
Do you really believe
that I am separate from you?
Whoa!
Where am I?
You're home.
It's hard to believe
we used to live here.
I must have seen you
or known you.
If only I could remember.
This is my old house, isn't it?
Let's go.
Please try.
- What is it?
- Nothing.
Really?
Damn it.
Okay, Betty.
What do you want to know?
What was in that room?
What are you afraid
that I'll see?
See? There's nothing.
It's empty.
What do you mean
I don't have access to him?
NSA has decided
to turn over study
of the threat to Atheon.
But you're head of the base.
I thought you were in charge.
But I don't set policy,
and I still take orders.
I can't believe Talbot
would go around me like this!
Oh, there's a lot of powerful
people that want in on this.
And money to be made,
lots of it.
You know the worst part
about all this?
When I had David Banner
locked up and sent that kid away,
I didn't give that boy a second
thought. He was just collateral damage.
Well, he isn't anymore, is he?
What can I do?
You can go home now.
I'd tell you to go and say good-bye,
but I've already been informed
that for now all further
contact is out of the question.
Right.
Hiya, Bruce. How ya feelin'?
Grub okay in here for ya?
- What do you want?
- That's a good question.
See, I need your cells to trigger
some chemical distress signals.
You know, so you can turn
a little green for me again,
and I can carve off
a piece of the real you,
analyze it, patent it,
make a fortune.
Do you mind?
I'll never let you.
I'm not sure you've got
much of a choice.
Come on, Bruce. Aren't
you feeling a little angry?
After all, you've only got
me to play with
now that Betty's dumped you
and gone back to Berkeley.
You're lying.
You know, for me
this is a win-win situation.
You turn green, and all these
guys come in and kill you,
and I perform the autopsy.
You don't...
And I mop the floor with you
and maybe by accident go
too far and break your neck.
Bad science, maybe,
but personally gratifying.
Come on, Bruce!
Let's see what you got.
Never
You know, consciously
you may control it,
but subconsciously,
I bet that's another story.
All right, let's jump-start
those brain waves.
Bruce.
My dear Miss Ross.
Welcome back.
There are two guards
right outside.
You don't have to worry. I'm
not angry with you. Not anymore.
What do you want?
It's over for me now.
I know that.
And soon it'll be
over for Bruce.
That's why I've come to you
to ask you if you could
persuade your father,
as a man, as a father himself,
that if I turn myself in now,
peacefully
and before
he puts me away forever,
that he would let me see my son
for one last time.
Could you do that for me?
It's out of
my father's hands now.
I understand.
He's a puppet now.
- I don't blame him.
- You shouldn't.
You should blame yourself for
what you've done to your son.
And what have I done to
my son, Miss Ross? Nothing.
I tried to improve
on the limits in myself.
Myself! Not him!
Can you understand?
To improve on nature.
My nature!
Knowledge of oneself!
It's the only path to the truth
that give men the power
to go beyond God's boundaries!
You know what's beyond
your boundaries? Other people.
All you've given Bruce is fear.
Fear of life.
Fear?
Perhaps, Miss Ross.
And loneliness, too.
Yes.
I feel them both.
But I have lived
completely once.
I was so much in love,
and she so much wanted a baby.
My baby.
I could tell
from the moment she conceived
that it wasn't a son
I had given her
but something else.
A monster, maybe.
I should have put
a stop to it right then,
but I was curious,
and that was my downfall.
And as I watched
this tiny life unfold,
I began to imagine
the horror of it,
and my curiosity was replaced
with compassion.
But they took away
my chance to cure him.
Your father threw me out.
- What are you doing?
- I remember that day so well,
every moment, every sensation
walking into the house,
the feeling of the handle
of the knife in my hand.
I knew I was doing a father's
work, fulfilling a father's mercy.
David, please stop it! No!
David, no! Talk to me! Listen!
But then she surprised me.
No! No!
David, no!
It was as if
she and the knife
merged.
No!
You cannot imagine
the unbearable finality of it.
And in that one moment,
I took everything
that was dear to me
and transformed it
into nothing more
than a memory.
Bingo! That must be some
jumbo nightmare he just had.
Okay, do it now.
Start the enzyme extraction.
Sir, negative
on drill penetration.
Damn it, drill him harder!
Give him full RPMs.
Come on, Holeman! Come on!
- Should I neutralize?
- No! I can't do anything with goop!
Come on!
All right, put him to sleep.
It's not stopping him!
Ready room, send in
our containment team.
Non-lethals only.
I repeat, non-lethals only.
I must have a sample of him.
Sir!
- Jesus!
- Hit him with the foam.
Deploy containment foam.
Talbot, talk to me.
Cease fire!
Under control, General. I'll
let you know if we need you.
Unacceptable. Unseat your
asses down there immediately.
I want a full-court evacuation
now. I'm shutting you down.
Lockdown.
- Didn't you hear what the General said?
- I said lockdown!
Clear! I need a sample of him!
Take it easy there, buddy.
This might give you
a bit of a sting here, Bruce.
- Fall back! Fall back!
- Clear your weapon! Clear it!
Give me the M2.
So long, big boy.
Clear!
Lockdown the entire
facility immediately.
Target's still moving
towards blue level.
Evacuate the main hall.
Send in backup, heavy weapons.
Issue general quarters.
Set firing lines left and right!
Heavy weapons, go, go, go!
Contamination, sir.
System readings are red line.
Data's on backup power supply.
Incoming!
- Shut down all power to the main hall.
- Sir?
Show him the way out.
We'll fight him outside.
Driver, stop. Driver, stop.
- Gunner, traverse left!
- Traverse left!
Clear back! Clear back!
Mr. President,
I have some bad news, sir.
Let's have it, General.
I've briefed the President
on Angry Man.
I assume that's what
this is about.
It is, ma'am.
I'm requesting a National
Command Authority override.
Angry Man is unsecure.
I need everything we have at my
disposal in order to stop his movement.
You're expecting
civilian casualties, General?
Not if I can help it, ma'am.
Consider it done.
Keep us posted.
Contact Goodman Control.
Patch data to the assets.
Contact H.Q.
Have them initiate
an immediate evacuation
in vicinity of
grid coordinates 6-5-15.
Confirm that the area
has been cleared.
Confirm area cleared.
- H.Q. confirms area cleared.
- Assets on-line, sir.
Gentlemen, it's time to dig in.
I want this target
stopped in his tracks.
Jesus.
Mayday! Mayday! Ah, shit!
Tango Four is down. Have
CSAR respond to our 20 ASAP.
We're okay, but, damn it, get
him off us before he tears us apart!
I've got no shot. Do you
have a clear line of fire?
Watch it, Tango Flight.
Break left! Break left!
Tango Three, pull back
and set up for a Hellfire shot.
Hold your fire
till we draw him off.
Tango One is hot. Gun wazzed.
Roger.
Going hot. Guns ready.
Engage at will.
Tango One,
pull back! Clear my line!
Tango Flight, clear back.
I've got him painted for Hellfire.
Roger that.
Tango One clear.
Take the shot.
- Tango One, Tango Three.
- I have contact.
Holy shit!
He's got my missile!
Mayday! Mayday!
Mayday! Mayday! We're hit!
We're going down!
Give me a head count.
Tango Three, give me a sit rep.
Our kite's busted up,
but we're okay.
Tango Flight, do you
have eyes on the target?
Tango One.
I have him in the rocks.
Salvo all.
Turn it into a parking lot.
T-bolt,
your parking lot is ready.
We're bingo
for fuel and ammo. R.T.B.
T-bolt, this is Goodman Control.
Be advised, target not
destroyed. He's on the move again.
Damn!
I've got it.
It appears he's heading home.
Launch fast movers. Have
them intercept and engage.
Hello?
Betty, Bruce got out.
He's headed your way
and probably right for you.
How far from the base are you?
I'm already here. They're
taking his father in now.
That's all good news.
Stay there, Betty.
- Legend One rolling in hot.
- Legend Two breaking off left.
I think I can come back around
for a gun attack.
Acquire a clear target.
Fire at will.
Increase altitude.
Civilian aircraft in vicinity.
Pull up! Pull up!
You're headed for the bridge!
I can't pull up!
Okay, you've got him now. Take
him on a ride to the top of the world.
Let's see what the thin air
will do for him.
Initiating afterburn.
I'm passing flight level 600.
This is out of my envelope.
Hang in there, Legend.
I can't maintain.
He's all over my aerodynamics.
He'll lose consciousness
before you.
Nine-fifty. I can't hold it.
I'm pulling back!
Puny human.
Contact. He's in the water.
All units, weapons hot.
Let's not take any chances.
You are cleared to fire
on target, Legend.
- Dad?
- Betty?
We don't have a choice.
I have to destroy him.
But you can't.
You will only fuel his rage,
and you will make him stronger.
It's you he's coming for.
You know that.
Then let me go to him.
Please.
Just give him a chance
to calm down.
All aircraft vicinity of San
Francisco, this is T-bolt on guard.
This area has been declared
restricted airspace.
All aircraft are ordered to
clear the airspace immediately.
Echo, One-niner.
Weapons are hot.
Target acquired.
Waiting your order to engage.
Repeat,
waiting your orders to engage.
Command code yellow.
Hold for authorization.
All units, hold your fire.
This is T-bolt to all assets.
You have direct orders
to hold your fire.
I repeat, hold your fire.
Echo, One-niner.
Roger that.
Go, go, go, go, go, go!
Hold your fire until my command!
- Engine 24 to command.
- We are in position now.
You found me.
You weren't that hard to find.
Yes, I was.
Let's take a walk.
That's the deal, gentlemen.
He stays on this base
until we get the final word from
C-3 on how to dispose of him.
In the meantime, if he does
anything but sit there in that chair,
we're gonna turn on the juice
and he'll be incinerated immediately.
We've established
a 200-yard perimeter, sir.
If we deploy
the electromagnetic array,
there should be
no collateral damage.
Here they come!
I'm doin' this for you, Betty.
But one way or another, we're
gonna have to prepare for the worst.
I should have killed you.
And I should have killed you.
I wish you had.
I saw her last night.
Saw her face.
Brown hair.
Brown eyes.
She smiled at me.
She reached down
and kissed my cheek.
I can almost remember a smell.
It was like desert flowers.
Her favorite perfume.
It's my mother, and I
don't even know her name.
It's all right, Son.
You go ahead and cry.
Go ahead and cry.
Cry. Crying will do you good.
Don't touch me!
Maybe once you were my father,
but you're not now
and you never will be.
Oh, is that so?
Well, I got news for you.
I didn't come here to see you.
I came here to see my son.
My real son.
The one inside of you.
You're nothing
but a superficial shell,
a husk of flimsy consciousness
ready to be torn off
at a moment's notice.
You can think what you like.
I don't care. Just go!
No, Son. Listen to me.
I found a cure.
For me.
My cells can transform, too,
absorb enormous
amounts of energy.
But, unlike you,
they're unstable.
Son, I need your strength.
I gave you life.
Now you must give it back to me!
Only a million times
more radiant, more powerful!
- Stop it.
- Stop? Stop what?
Stop what?
Think about all those men
out there in their uniforms,
barking and swallowing orders,
inflicting their petty rule
over the entire globe!
Think of all the harm
they've done!
To you! To me!
To humanity!
And know this,
that we can make them
and their flags and their
anthems and their governments
disappear in a flash!
You in me.
I'd rather die.
Oh, that's your answer?
Then indeed you shall die
and be reborn
a hero of the kind
that walked the earth
long before the pale
religions of civilization
infected humanity's soul!
Go!
Stop your bawling,
you weak little speck
of human trash.
All right. I'll go!
- You just watch me go!
- Hit it.
Hit it again!
We can't, sir.
There's no power.
Some kind of
counter-electromagnetic field.
Move in and assault
the target. Move in!
Move, move, move!
Sir, I've located them
on radar. Pear Lake.
Call up the task force.
Yes.
That's right. Keep fighting.
The more you fight,
the more of you I take.
Strange. We're reading a
phenomenal drop in temperatures there.
Simultaneous
radiological activity.
They're absorbing
all the ambient energy.
Relax.
Sleep now, Bruce,
and forget forever.
Struggle no more
and give me all of your power.
You think you can
live with it? Take it!
Take it all!
Oh, yes! Yes!
Take it back!
It's not stopping!
Gentlemen, release.
Gamma charge away.
Sweet dreams.
- Hello?
- Betty, is that you?
- Hi, Dad.
- I'm glad I caught you.
- I'm glad you called.
- Thanks.
Look, Betty, you and I...
Well, we both know that Bruce
couldn't have survived that blast.
But... Well, you know...
- What is it?
- Well, you know.
The usual loonies,
seein' things.
Only now everything's green.
Right.
Look...
If by some chance
he did survive,
and he should try to contact
you, try to get in touch,
you'd tell me, wouldn't you?
No, I wouldn't.
But you know as well as I do,
I wouldn't have to.
I mean, my phones are bugged,
my computer's tapped.
I'm under surveillance.
I'll tell you, though,
that if he were alive,
I'm the last person
I would want him to come to
because as much as
I miss him, I...
I loved him. I...
Yeah.
I'm sorry, Betty.
I am so sorry.
I know you are.